<androidx.coordinatorlayout.widget.CoordinatorLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:id="@+id/coordinatorLayout"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout
        android:id="@+id/appBarLayout"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="200dp"
        android:theme="@style/ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Dark.ActionBar">

        <com.google.android.material.appbar.CollapsingToolbarLayout
            android:id="@+id/collapsingToolbarLayout"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            app:contentScrim="?attr/colorPrimary"
            app:layout_scrollFlags="scroll|exitUntilCollapsed">

            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/ivParallax"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:scaleType="centerCrop"
                android:src="@drawable/alert_drop"
                app:layout_collapseMode="parallax"
                app:layout_collapseParallaxMultiplier="0.7" />

            <androidx.appcompat.widget.Toolbar
                android:id="@+id/toolbar"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="?attr/actionBarSize"
                app:title="Our Mission"
                app:layout_collapseMode="pin"
                app:popupTheme="@style/ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Light"
                app:theme="@style/ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Dark.ActionBar" />
        </com.google.android.material.appbar.CollapsingToolbarLayout>
    </com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout>

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/text"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:fillViewport="true"
        android:text="He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau.


        So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. He made climate change one of his signature issuers. He's Justin Trudeau. So in a country like Canada, you'd think his reelection would be a landslide. "
        app:layout_behavior="@string/appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">


    </TextView>

</androidx.coordinatorlayout.widget.CoordinatorLayout>